Diane Wolkstein collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Story Drafts
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - Darkness in California draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Echindna Dreaming, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Egypt story drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Esther's Story drafts, circa 1980s, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Goose with the Golden Feathers draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/11)
    - The Grass Slipper drafts, 1994-1996, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/12)
    - Haitian Tales drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Hans Christian Andersen retellings drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Icelandic stories drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Isis and Osiris drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Jewish stories drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Judith draft, 2001, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Khotan draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/19)
    - The Lion Prince drafts, 1977, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Little Mouse's Painting drafts, circa 1992, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Looking for the Story drafts, 1977-1978, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/1)
    - The Magic Orange Trees draft (1 of 2), undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/2)
    - The Magic Orange Trees draft (2 of 2), undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/3)
    - The Magic Orange Trees proof copy, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/4)
    - The Magic Orange Trees recording, 1982, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/5)
    - The Magic Orange Trees source art, circa 1973, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 22/2)
    - The Magic Orange Trees source art, 1977-1978, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/5)
    - The Magic Wings draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Miss Hirsch draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/7)
    - The Monkey King drafts, 2009, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/8)
    - The Monkey King drafts, 2010, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/9)
    - The Monkey King drafts (1 of 3), circa 2010, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/10)
    - The Monkey King drafts (2 of 3), circa 2010, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 6/11)
    - The Monkey King drafts (3 of 3), circa 2010, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/1)
    - The Monkey King in Mandarin, circa 2010, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Ocean Visits Sun and Moon draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Oom Razoom draft, 2007, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Poem drafts (1 of 3), undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Poem drafts (2 of 3), undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Poem drafts (3 of 3), undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Popol Vuh draft, 1994, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Popol Vuh draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Questions?? A Collection of Folk Tales for Children of All Ages draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Red Boy draft, 2010, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/10)
    - The Red Lion drafts, circa 1977, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/11)
    - The Red Lion drafts, 1992, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Short stories, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/13)
    - Song drafts, 1987, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/7)
    - Song drafts notebook, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Songs - singing and guitar drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Squirrel's Song drafts, circa 1976, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 7/15)
    - The Story of Ruth drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Sunmother Wakes the World draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Tibetan stories draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/3)
    - Treasures of the Heart illustrations, 2002, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/4)
    - Treasures of the Heart drafts (1 of 3), 2002, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Treasures of the Heart drafts (2 of 3), 2002, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/6)
    - Treasures of the Heart drafts (3 of 3), 2002, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/7)
    - The Vindlander Saga draft, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/8)
    - The Visit drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/9)
    - The White Wave drafts, 1979, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/9)
    - Zo-Zo drafts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 8/10)
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Little Mouse's Painting cover draft, circa 1992, 1 color negative (4x5 in.); AFC 2016/057: PH207 (Box 26)
    - Abulafia Dream Songs cover draft, undated, 1 color negative (4x5 in.); AFC 2016/057: PH213 (Box 26)
    - Inanna art, undated, 2 color slides; AFC 2016/057: PH202 - PH203 (Box 23)
- Series 3: Story Performances
  Photographs, programs, scripts, and audio and video recordings of Wolkstein's storytelling performances at various venues. Includes materials from her work as a storyteller in Central Park.
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    Arranged into groupings by file type, including performance photographs, programs, and scripts. Arranged chronologically within these groupings.
    - Photographs
      - Performance photographs, circa 1960s, 2 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Performance photographs, 1967, 5 black-and-white photographic prints and 1 black-and-white contact sheet (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Performance photographs, 1968, 12 color photographic prints (Box-folder 8/13)
      - Hans Christian Andersen stories in Denmark, 1969, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 17 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Hospital storytelling performances, November 1969, 4 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Performance photographs, 1969, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 23 black-and-white photographic prints and 5 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Performance photographs, circa 1970s, 16 black-and-white photographic prints and 2 color photographic prints (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Performance photographs, 1970, AFC 2016/057: PH249 and AFC 2016/057: PH250.; 19 black-and-white photographic prints, 14 color photographic prints, and 2 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Performance photographs, 1971, 3 color photographic prints (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Performance photographs, 1972, 21 black-and-white photographic prints and 1 black-and-white contact sheet (Box-folder 9/1)
      - Performance photographs, 1973, 6 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 9/2)
      - Queen of Denmark's visit, 1976, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 4 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 9/3)
      - Performance photographs, 1977, 4 black-and-white photographic prints and 1 black-and-white contact sheet (Box-folder 9/4)
      - Performance photographs, 1978, 8 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 9/5)
      - Performance photographs, circa 1980s, 16 black-and-white photographic prints, 16 color photographic prints, and 3 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 9/6)
      - Performance photographs, 1984-2007, 76 color photographic prints and 6 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 9/7)
      - Performance photographs, circa 1990s, AFC 2016/057: PH342, AFC 2016/057: PH345, AFC 2016/057: PH346, and AFC 2016/057: PH348.; 2 black-and-white photographic prints, 31 color photographic prints, 11 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 9/8)
      - Performance photographs, 1990-1991, 8 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 9/9)
      - Central Park storytelling photographs, 1997-2001, 96 color photographic prints and 1 black-and-white photographic print (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Performance photographs, circa 2000s, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 14 color photographic prints (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Inanna performance photographs, 2000, AFC 2016/057: PH006.; 1 folder of manuscript materials with 5 color photographic prints, 5 black-and-white photographic prints, and 4 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Michigan Storytelling Festival, October 22-23, 2004, afc2016057_dc088; 38 color photographs (JPG)
      - Performance photographs, 2004, 1 color photographic print (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Storytelling in Central Park, September 16, 2006, afc2016057_dc053; 31 color photographs (JPG)
      - Shirley Keller and Diane Wolkstein performance, June 22, 2007, afc2016057_dc094; 22 color photographs (JPG)
      - Celebrate Story Festival photographs, June 22-23, 2007, afc2016057_dc271; 147 color photographs (JPG)
      - Celebrate Story Festival photographs, 2007, afc2016057_dc258; 1,045 color photographs (JPG)
      - Hurricane Katrina Benefit performance, November 10, 2007, afc2016057_dc052; 137 color photographs (JPG)
      - Performance photographs, 2007, afc2016057_dc123; 199 color photographs (JPG)
      - Performance photographs, circa 2009, afc2016057_dc127; 39 color photographs (JPG)
      - Storytelling in Central Park, circa 2010, afc2016057_dc336; 4 color photographs (JPG)
      - Toronto Festival of Storytelling photographs, 2010, afc2016057_dc328; 50 color photographs (JPG)
      - Performance photographs, January 23, 2012, afc2016057_dc036; 84 color photographs (JPG)
      - Inanna performance photographs, undated, AFC 2016/057: PH010, AFC 2016/057: PH205, and AFC 2016/057: PH206.; 1 folder of manuscript materials with 52 color photographic prints, 7 black-and-white photographic prints, and 2 black-and-white contact sheets (Box-folder 9/14)
      - Magic Orange Trees and Owl performances, undated, 21 color photographic prints (Box-folder 9/15)
      - Performance photographs, undated, 15 black-and-white photographic prints, 1 black-and-white contact sheet, and 13 color photographic prints (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Storytelling photographs, undated, AFC 2016/057: PH002, AFC 2016/057: PH003, and AFC 2016/057: PH004.; 22 black-and-white photographic prints, 3 black-and-white contact sheets, and 11 color photographic prints (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Programs
      - Programs, 1984-2006, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Programs, 2007, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Programs, 2008, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Programs, 2009, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 10/5)
      - Programs, 2010, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 10/6)
      - Programs, 2011, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 10/7)
      - Programs, 2012, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 10/8)
    - Scripts and performance notes
      - Inanna ballet, 2001, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 14 color photographic prints (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Inanna opera, 2004, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Inanna annotated by Wolkstein, 2009, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Monkey King performance, circa 2009, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/1)
      - Inanna annotated by Wolkstein, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/2)
      - Monkey King performance lighting cues, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Monkey King performance notes, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Monkey King performance script, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Performance scripts, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Hans Christian Andersen stories in Denmark, 1969, 1 black-and-white negative (8x10 in.); AFC 2016/057: PH334 (Box 25)
    - Storytelling, circa 1970s, 36 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH351 (Box 25)
    - Performance photographs, 1970, 23 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH249; Box-Folder 8/18 for contact sheet print of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Performance photographs, 1970, 34 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH250; Box-Folder 8/18 for contact sheet print of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Performance photographs, 1978, 35 color slides; AFC 2016/057: PH214 - PH248 (Box 24)
    - Performance photographs, circa 1980s, 2 color slides; AFC 2016/057: PH349 - PH350 (Box 24)
    - Performance photographs, 1984-2007, 33 color negatives (35mm); 6 black-and-white negatives (4x5 in.); AFC 2016/057: PH001 (Box 25, Box 26)
    - Performance photographs, circa 1990s, 37 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH342; Box-Folder 9/8 for contact sheet prints of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Performance photographs, circa 1990s, 41 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH345; Box-Folder 9/8 for contact sheet prints of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Performance photographs, circa 1990s, 7 color slides; AFC 2016/057: PH335 - PH341 (Box 24)
    - Tricksters performance photographs, circa 1990s, 87 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH346; Box-Folder 9/8 for contact sheet prints of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Storytelling, 1990, 74 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH348; Box-Folder 9/8 for contact sheet prints of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Storytelling, 1991, 1 black-and-white negatives (4x5 in.); AFC 2016/057: PH347 (Box 25)
    - Storytelling performance, June 1992, 36 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH343 (Box 25)
    - Inanna performance photographs, 2000, 22 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH006; Box-Folder 9/12 for contact sheet prints of these negatives. (Box 26)
    - American Museum of Natural History video photographs, undated, 3 color slides; AFC 2016/057: PH007 - PH009 (Box 23)
    - Inanna performance photographs, undated, 1 black-and-white negative (4x5 in.); AFC 2016/057: PH010; Box-Folder 9/14 for prints of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Inanna performance photographs, undated, 15 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH201 (Box 26)
    - Inanna performance photographs, undated, 2 color negatives (4x5 in.); AFC 2016/057: PH204 (Box 26)
    - Inanna performance photographs, undated, 40 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH205; Box-Folder 9/14 for prints of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Inanna performance photographs, undated, 26 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH206; Box-Folder 9/14 for prints of these negatives. (Box 26)
    - Inanna performance photographs, undated, 41 color slides; AFC 2016/057: PH293 - PH333 (Box 23)
    - Performance photographs, undated, 4 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH252 (Box 26)
    - Song of Songs performance photographs, undated, 25 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH012 (Box 26)
    - Song of Songs performance photographs, undated, 3 black-and-white negatives (4x5 in.); AFC 2016/057: PH013 (Box 25)
    - Storytelling photographs, undated, 32 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH002; Box-Folder 10/1 for contact sheet prints of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Storytelling photographs, undated, 31 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH003; Box-Folder 10/1 for contact sheet prints of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Storytelling photographs, undated, 22 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH004; Box-Folder 10/1 for contact sheet prints of these negatives. (Box 25)
    - Storytelling photographs, undated, 5 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH199 (Box 26)
    - Storytelling photographs, undated, 8 color negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH344 (Box 26)
    - Tristan and Iseult at Open Center, undated, 63 black-and-white negatives (35mm); AFC 2016/057: PH355 (Box 25)
  - Subseries 3: Audio and Video
    - 25 Years, 1982, AFC 2016/057: MV018; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - 40 Year celebration, June 22, 2007, afc2016057_dc049; Ceremony and performance at Central Park Arsenal.; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Action Poetry, Tape #16, 1994, AFC 2016/057: MV321; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Side A: American Folk Tales; Side B: English Folk Tales, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR094; 1 sound cassette
    - American Stories, July 4, 1998, AFC 2016/057: SR095; 1 sound cassette
    - Armoury Show, undated
      - Part 1, AFC 2016/057: MV026; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2, AFC 2016/057: MV027; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - The Bacchae Tape, undated
      - Hi8 version, AFC 2016/057: MV322; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
      - U-matic version, AFC 2016/057: MV326; 1 videocassette (U-matic)
    - Bad Baby Pirate, Tickey O Tickey Rum, Grow Orange Trees, June 1973, AFC 2016/057: SR096; 1 sound cassette
    - The Banza, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR097; 1 sound cassette
    - Bible Stories Retold, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR098; 1 sound cassette
    - Biblical Stories, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR099; 1 sound cassette
    - Birthday for Bird, March 4, 1970, AFC 2016/057: SR100; 1 sound tape reel: 5 in.
    - Celebrate Story Festival, 2007
      - Part 1.1, AFC 2016/057: MV028; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 1.2, AFC 2016/057: MV029; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 1.3, AFC 2016/057: MV030; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 1.4, AFC 2016/057: MV031; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 1.5, AFC 2016/057: MV032; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 1.6, AFC 2016/057: MV033; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2.1, AFC 2016/057: MV034; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2.2, AFC 2016/057: MV035; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2.3, AFC 2016/057: MV036; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2.4, AFC 2016/057: MV037; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2.5, AFC 2016/057: MV038; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2.6, AFC 2016/057: MV039; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 3.1, AFC 2016/057: MV040; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 3.2, AFC 2016/057: MV041; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 3.3, AFC 2016/057: MV042; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 3.4, AFC 2016/057: MV043; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 4.1, AFC 2016/057: MV044; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 4.2, AFC 2016/057: MV045; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 4.4, AFC 2016/057: MV046; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 4.5, AFC 2016/057: MV047; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 5.1, AFC 2016/057: MV048; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 5.2, AFC 2016/057: MV049; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 5.3, AFC 2016/057: MV050; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 5.4, AFC 2016/057: MV051; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 5.5, AFC 2016/057: MV052; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - CelebrateStory Festival audience shots, 2008, AFC 2016/057: MV053; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, September 13, 1994
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV022; Close up. American Museum of Natural History, Diane Wolkstein and Shlomo Carlebach; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV023; Distance. American Museum of Natural History, Diane Wolkstein and Shlomo Carlebach; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV024; Edit #2. American Museum of Natural History, Diane Wolkstein and Shlomo Carlebach; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR093; American Museum of Natural History, Diane Wolkstein and Shlomo Carlebach; 1 sound cassette
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV062; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV063; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV064; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV067; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV068; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV069; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc104; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, June 1997, AFC 2016/057: MV021; Edit #1. American Museum of Natural History, Diane Wolkstein and Shlomo Carlebach; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, June 2, 1999, AFC 2016/057: MV054; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, June 20, 1999, AFC 2016/057: MV025; Edit #3. American Museum of Natural History, Diane Wolkstein and Shlomo Carlebach; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, June 22, 1999
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV055; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV056; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR101; 1 sound cassette
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR102; 1 sound cassette
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, June 4, 2004, AFC 2016/057: MV057; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, 2004, AFC 2016/057: MV058; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV059; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV060; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV061; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV065; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV066; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV070; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Celebrating Our Mistakes, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR103; 1 sound cassette
    - Central Park 40th anniversary performance, June 1, 1996
      - Part 1 - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV019; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2 - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV020; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV071; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Chasidic Stories, undated, afc2016057_dc043; Live! At the Toronto Public Library with musical guests Drew Jurecka and Rebekah Wolkstein.; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - Cinderella - Russia, June 1988, AFC 2016/057: SR106; 1 sound cassette
    - Cinderella, October 1988, AFC 2016/057: SR104; 1 sound cassette
    - Cinderella - Margo Speicher, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR105; 1 sound cassette
    - The Cool Ride in the Sky, 1987, afc2016057_dc030; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - The Cool Ride in the Sky, 1992, Diane Wolkstein accompanied by Shirley Keller
      - Part 1, afc2016057_dc108; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Part 2, afc2016057_dc107; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - The Cool Ride in the Sky, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV329; 1 videocassette (DVCam)
    - Cool Ride, Magic Wings, Banza, Emperor's New Clothes, June 6, 1987, Performed at Hans Christian Andersen statue
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV073; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc084; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Cotsen Storytellers Series, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV074; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - The Courtship of Inanna and Dumuzi, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR107; 1 sound cassette
    - Dance Dance Dolly Mine; Mouse Tales; Old Witch, June 6, 1975, AFC 2016/057: SR108; 1 sound cassette